I, it's odd to me how so many people can seem so confused by trans people's experience of not
feeling themselves in their body. I think all of us have at some point in our lives
felt like we were living outside of who we felt we were. And that can be in a number of different
scenarios. It can be as basic as being at a job where you're just like, I'm having to cold switch
every day. And this feels crazy because I'm living a lie eight hours of the day or as extreme as I
feel like a gendered woman. And yet I was born in a world that assigns my gender to my sex.
And I was born with a penis. So much of transphobia is just not only a lack of compassion,
right? But also a lack of introspection, true human introspection into the human condition.
And the fact that what may have seemed so simple for you could be so complicated for someone else.
and that that right there is the most normal human experience out here.